The people in this video take being lucky to the extreme.
From finding a $250 million lottery ticket on the street.
to winning the championship game with a full court basketball
shot.
That's extremely lucky.
NASCAR crew dodges two cars.
Dude, I love NASCAR.
Into the danger zone.
Jason takes it.
Jason, you're in the danger zone.
Jason, man.
Jason, gosh darn it, get out of the danger zone.
Jason, you're not Jason Bourne.
Jason don't know nothing but jacking.
Look at him.
He jumped with a floor jack.
Those things weigh like 60 pounds.
That's insane.
All right, so they're riding a roller coaster,
and he catches someone's phone that fell off a different roller coaster.
Wait, because now he can probably look through that guy's phone
and embarrass him and stuff, and that's pretty funny.
Imagine falling from this.
Imagine dragging.
Yo, they were asking for that to happen once, dude.
Oh, boy.
Those are blanks.
Okay, those are blanks.
Yeah, it was probably just the air.
I don't know.
Oh, well, it looked like there might
have been a little projectile.
So this is your local WWE.
Did you see the guy on the side?
He was like, yo, turn around.
You just did the coolest thing I've ever seen.
OK, so he's jumping up.
Oh!
Wow.
Oh.
I don't know if that was luck.
That looked like skill.
What is this?
This is tree falling.
Noni?
Nice, he made a new tree.
OK, OK, I'll prove.
I'll prove.
All right, gentlemen, this is why you should always
Always wear safety goggles.
Number one, I saw this on TikTok.
Number two, it's proven fake.
I want to believe it's real.
No.
It's on the internet.
It's fake.
Everything on the internet is fake.
I just want to believe that he saw it and gets snaps in half
and that catches it.
That's so cool.
I watched a long video about this.
He was in like a submarine.
It sank to the bottom.
It had an air pocket.
It was on the bottom of the ocean.
He was living in an air pocket in pitch black for four days.
He felt sharks swimming around him and everything and freezing cold water did and they got him out
Yeah, they got him out high five for that guy. This is a state championship game the team in black
He's currently up by three points. Oh
Look half a second left on the clock. Wait a minute Jimmy where he's standing it approximately would be worth three points
No chance. He makes it you know, that's sick
This is why I'm scared of baseball I got hit in the face with a ball like that one time look at that Wow
Dude, it literally, like, went across his chest.
Just catch it.
What do you mean, just catch it?
He tried.
Just catch it.
This is why I don't ice climb.
This is like that Modern Warfare 2 mission.
It kind of looked like he hit...
He's only climbing with those two sheets.
And his feet have spikes on them, is the only other thing.
Oh, my gosh.
No rope, no nothing, dude.
If you lose your footing, it's just that one thing holding you up.
No, never ice climbing.
Whoa.
That's an...
Oh, might have been an accident.
Stay in your lane.
Yeah, it's an accident.
they collided this guy's knocked out just blacked out wow nice he just saved his life all right so
these workers are working on a building whoa that's like a minecraft sand trap oh my god
look at that guy on the pole he's just like this is the safest spot i know it he bought a lottery
ticket a winning lottery ticket but he left it at the store and thankfully an honest cashier
came to the rescue you work at a gas station someone buys a lottery ticket they leave it there
Mm-hmm you grab it next day you finds out it wins a quarter of a billion dollars. You're giving it back
You keeping it to the bank. I would anonymously leave him a million dollars
So yeah, maybe two million, but look that's on you finders keepers losers weepers. Oh
Wow, bro, come on we do team trees and this type a is back by their nature cheese that tree said, hmm. It's your time
Oh, Christmas lights. This is why I don't hang Christmas lights.
Oh, oh.
Dude, imagine not being alive anymore because you're hanging Christmas lights.
Oh, thank gosh he had help.
Wow, he had a lot of help.
It's like they were just waiting for it to happen.
Yo, if I ever fall off a roof, I better have six dudes come help me.
Okay, so he's driving.
Getting a lot of sway going.
Yeah, he's noticing.
Oh, Lord have mercy.
Dang.
Oh, what's going to happen? Oh, wait, is it loose?
No, it's still connected. It's a trailer, but it's getting like sideways man. He handled that incredibly never let him know your next move
This clip has the title card of an inch away and before we watch the clip
I just want to say I don't understand why that's in the world's luckiest clips because that seems pretty far away an inch is a ton
Of space some would say it's it's almost a little too much. I mean he still hit that sign through that sign
move your car now skater oh that was a pretty cool trick in itself kid you are what chris wishes he
was hey no what i wish i was was that subrette hot dog because that thing looked good the best
evasive maneuver i've ever seen oh kicking drywall is so much fun
a lot went wrong so quick but also right
don't have to know sports to know that was sick west brick capitalized on the brick he did that
was beautiful that was very cool crazy ping pong saves oh he's only got one arm whoa that's cool
congrats to you he didn't even react that's how you know he's been there before oh that's a giant
hole right oh am i looking at a hole what am i looking at oh oh my goodness wow how does the guy
who's currently standing there feel safe he's like let me get closer to the edge just so you can see
it humans are dumb like i love people but humans are really dumb we've all seen this clip all
right just getting interviewed boom it was that fake did that happen did that turn out fake i
don't know it's kind of hard to believe it's real because watch see it's coming coming he gets it
Oh, but wait, you can't this isn't a picture. You can only photoshop pictures. You can't photoshop a video so far
I'd say these people are pretty lucky. Yeah, lucky. We didn't call him out sooner on their fakeness. Oh
He hit the mother load three or four other people's unluckiest day became his luckiest day ever. Does he get it? Oh
Really you're he's in too deep
oh shake it shake it kick it why would you not just kick it this is intense he can do it oh
come on go on nice he got the whole lot bro look at that genuine excitement he's like oh
we had to pay for half these chips oh my god if you haven't already hit the subscribe button
we're gonna let someone random to subscribe to the next seven days fly here and lightly
punch chris like this so if you want to punch chris subscribe it's got to be light